brunoscholz@yahoo.de

Bruno Ribeiro Scholz

ABOUT ME

Developer with 15+ years of experience in diverse fields and an entrepreneurial view, my goal is always to create value by generating intelligent solutions that fulfill client's needs. I like situations that require the use of multiple skills and critical thinking. As a skilled life-long student, I'm now diving into the blockchain rabbit-hole while deepening my knowledge in fullstack tools.

EXPERIENCE

POSSIBLE / WUNDERMAN THOMPSON TECH

Frontend Engineer - Angular, React, Drupal

January 2021 - Current

Becoming fullstack Drupal. Held a few client technical meetings and some solo projects. Several projects for clients like Siemens, DWS and SporTV.

OCTION

Co-Founder & Game Developer - Unity3D(C#), Angular, Python, PHP, Mysql

February 2014 - August 2016

Creating products directed to corporate training, advergames for business fairs and educational games.

Banco do Brasil

PHP, MySql, VBA

May 2006 - February 2014

Worked together with engineering and logistics management in Manaus (AM) in the development of a dashboard for cost control in building and renovation projects.

ABBRA

Developer - PHP, MySql

April 2004 - May 2006

Development of dynamic processes, from contract to complete legal process with customer leads, batch research and verification in court databases for more than one million potential clients.

EDUCATION

UDEMY.COM

Solidity Ethereum Developer: Build Blockchain DApps – Javascript, Solidity, Truffle, Web3

2017, 2021

UNIVERSIDADE POSITIVO, Curitiba

Digital Games - Unity3D, 3DSMax, C#, Javascript
2013 - 2015 (incomplete)

UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL DO AMAZONAS, Manaus

Computer Science - Haskell, Python
2011 - 2013 (incomplete)

UNIVERSIDADE TECNOLÓGICA FEDERAL DO PARANÁ, Curitiba

Electrical Engineering - Electronics and Telecommunication - c, c++

2003 - 2006 (incomplete)